好的  已经完成
Alright you're done.
现在看下我的解决方案
Let's take a look at my solution.
对于删除方法来说  是很直接的
For the delete method things are pretty straight forward.
我们只需调用db.delete函数  函数参数包括合适的table和selection
We just called db.delete with the appropriate table, and the selection,
和selectionArgs
and the selection arguments.
一种要考虑的情况是  如果selection为null  那就让selection赋值为1
One thing that I've done is if the selection is null I set it to one.
这能删除所有的行  并返回删除的行的数量
This makes delete all rows return the number of rows deleted.
这很有用的
And that can be useful.
只在一种情况下，我会通知ContentResolver发生了一个变化
I only notify the content resolver of a change
即当我们的确删除了某些行时
if we actually have deleted some rows.
但是严格讲并非一定要这么做
This isn't strictly necessary.
Update方法看起来的确像Delete方法
Update looks almost exactly like Delete.
我们再看  基于URI我们选择不同的表
Once again, based upon the URI we select a different table and
调用update方法  并给参数selectionArgs赋不同的值
call the update function with the values in the selection arguments.
并且我只在我们确实更新了某些行时进行通知
And I only notify for a change we've actually updated some rows.
好
Alright.
让我们来测试一下我们的方法
Let's go to test our function.
在测试用例里面  你可以看到我们把testDeleteRecords方法反注释掉
In test provider you can see we've uncommented out test delete records
同样反注释testUpdateLocation方法
as well as test update location.
让我们运行一下  以保证这都能正常运行
Let's run the test to make sure everything works correctly.
你能看到所有运行通过
And as you can see everything passes.
我们已经正确完成更新和删除
We've done everything correct for updating and
ContentProvider的所有内容
deleting the content provider.